https://www.litesourceinc.com/privacy-policy/

Security & Privacy Information
Lite Source, Inc. is committed to establishing and maintaining our customers' confidence and trust. This privacy statement acknowledges our responsibility and commitment to protecting the personal, business and financial information you provide online. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website www.litesourceinc.com.
Use of Collected Information
Lite Source, Inc. will not collect any personal information about you  unless you provide it to us voluntarily or unless otherwise permitted by applicable laws and regulations for the protection of your personal information. The information you supply will be used to respond to inquiries, notify you of promotions and announcements if you have previously provided your permission, or to supply you with requested information on products and services.
Visitors to our site are free to browse and explore without providing any information. Our site's checkout requires users to provide contact information (name, address, phone, fax, e-mail, etc.) This information is used to enable and complete transactions, to send materials about our company and to contact customers when necessary. If you do not want your personal information collected, please do not submit it to us.
Financial information submitted (customer number, credit card number, credit references, resale number, etc.) is used to qualify a customer and to bill for products and services. This information is required to complete a transaction. Financial information received from third parties (i.e. credit references supplied by the customer) become part of a customer's private history and is kept in the strictest confidence.
Lite Source, Inc. will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties and will only share if necessary to complete a transaction or specific request of our customer or if required by law.
There are some instances in which we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. For example, we may document the type of computer operating system you are using or the type of Internet browser you are operating or your IP address. This information is used to gather broad demographic information that is used only by Lite Source, Inc. to improve our business practices.
Use of Cookies
When you view the Lite Source, Inc. website we may store some data on your computer in the form of a “cookie” which may be used to create an improved website. A cookie is a small file that is placed on your computer that will interact with our site in order to remember preferences with the intent of providing a better user experience. Most web browsers automatically allow cookies to be stored. However, if you do not want to receive cookies it is possible to turn them off. Please refer to your browser instructions and configure your Internet browser to erase all cookies from your hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Certain areas of www.litesourceinc.com may not be fully functional if cookies are turned off.
Security of Collected Information
Lite Source, Inc. utilizes technical security measures, such as firewalls and secured socket layers (SSL), to safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access or disclosure with respect to business transactions being conducted through www.litesourceinc.com. We also have in place managerial and physical safeguards to protect your information.
Controlling your information - Opt-In/Opt-Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. If you have previously submitted information and would like for us to remove it from our system, we will make all reasonable attempts to delete your information from our files. If you believe any information we hold to be incorrect or incomplete, please follow the instructions below or contact us so that we may promptly correct the informatin. To request information updates and/or removal; or to opt-out of receiving communications after you have agreed to opt-in, you can send your request via:
Login www.litesourceinc.com - My Account - Manage Communications
www.litesourceinc.com - Contact Us
E-mail to customerservice@litesourceinc.com
Mail to the following postal address: PO Box 991139 Louisville, KY 40269
Users can update their online account information by using the following methods:
To update address information:
www.litesourceinc.com  - My Account -  Address Book
To update email address & password:
www.litesourceinc.com -  My Account -  Address Information
Users may request details of personal information held within our company. If you would like a copy of the information, please mail your request to:
Lite Source Inc.
Attn: Data Control Officer
PO Box 991139
Louisville, KY 40269
Links to other sites
Our site may include links to other websites. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party sites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, other such websites.
Descriptions and Information
The product descriptions and information on this site are based on information shared with us by our suppliers and based on our own information. Lite Source, Inc. is not responsible for inaccuracies or errors made inadvertently. Should you find an error in the information presented on this site, please contact us.
Children
This website is not intended for persons under 13 years of age, and we do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children. Our products are intended for use by providers of healthcare, and we do not knowingly market our products or services to children.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions or comments about this privacy policy, please refer to the contact us page. We welcome any suggestions you may have.
Changes to this Policy
We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the Effective Date below. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. Your continued use of www.litesourceinc.com constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.
Effective date: May 24, 2018
Newsletter Sign Up
Subscribe
Site resources
International Shipping
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Top Brands
Copyright 2018 Lite Source Inc.
